I PUTU GEDE PRAMA DUTA

Jakarta, Indonesia | Email: putu.duta@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Fresh graduate with a Computer Science degree from Universitas Bina Nusantara. Have experience as an application developer during an internship at PT Freeport Indonesia. Have high motivation and willingness to learn especially things related to computer science.

EXPERIENCE

PT Freeport Indonesia – Jakarta, Indonesia

Application Developer Intern (February 2022 – February 2023)

- Responsible for supporting and maintaining the current and new application in the Management Information System Division.
- Develop, implement, and maintain various applications that support the organization's operations in collaboration with other teams.

Bina Nusantara IT Division - Jakarta, Indonesia

Associate Member (March 2021 - February 2022)

• Part of the Software Solution Group 3 Cluster 2 which is responsible for applications development on the Binus Corp website. Learning & Dev., Knowledge Management, and Binus Square.

Bina Nusantara English Club - Jakarta, Indonesia

Assistant Manager of Information Technology Division (March 2021 – March 2022)

- Assist the Manager to lead 4 IT staff.
- Help develop and maintain websites for the organization.
- Provide training to staff in developing website applications using Laravel.

Bina Nusantara English Club - Jakarta, Indonesia

Staff of Information Technology Division (March 2020 – March 2021)

- Create, develop and maintain BNEC Website, Such as Social Event Website, Recruitment Website and Asian English Olympics Website.
- Learn how to develop a website with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, and Laravel Framework.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITAS BINA NUSANTARA (2019 - 2023)

Bachelor of Computer Science - GPA 3.86

SKILLS

Technical Skills: Laravel, PHP, SQL, C#, .NET, HTML, CSS, Javascript

Certifications: Great Learning .NET Fundamentals (2023)